Guide to the Human Rights Campaign records, 1975-2015.
Human Rights Campaign records, 1975-2015
- Series V. Grassroots Organizing and Mailgrams
  - Field Division and Speak Out, 1988 -
    - Subject Files
      - Gay / Lesbian Parents, 1997-8 (Box 22, Folder 21)
      - G/L Parenting "National Survey on Gay Family Issues", 1997 (Box 22, Folder 22)
      - Hate Crime Stats (reports ), 1997 (Box 22, Folder 23)
      - HIV / AIDS, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 24)
      - Impact Illinois, 1998-99 (Box 22, Folder 25)
      - International, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 26)
      - Opposition - Jerry Falwell (Box 22, Folder 27)
      - HRC - Marriage, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 28)
      - Marriage (Box 22, Folder 29)
      - Marriage - Report "Research on Orgs Opposing Same Sex Marriage", 1997 (Box 22, Folder 30)
      - NCOP, 1997-98 (Box 22, Folder 31)
      - "Opposition Primer" by the Pro-choice Resource Ctr. 1996 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - HRC - Out There - Talking Points, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - PFAW Report "Hostile Climate", 1995 (Box 23, Folder 3)
      - People of Faith, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 4)
      - Political Retreat (HRCF staff), 1995 (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - Pride, 1996-7 (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - Radical Right (Box 23, Folder 7)
      - Sex Panic, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 8)
      - State Initiatives - Ballot Initiative Strategy Center, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 9)
      - State Plans, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 10)
      - Transgender - AEGIS, 1995-6 (Box 23, Folder 11)
      - Transgender Issues, 1997-99 (Box 23, Folder 12)
      - U.S. OPM - non-discrimination policy, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 13)
      - HRC internal - Transgender Issues, 1996-98 (Box 54, Folder 26)
      - HRC Workplace Discrimination, 1997 (Box 78, Folder 22)
      - National Organizations
        - DC-ACLU, 1994-97 (Box 21, Folder 51)
        - AFL-CIO-Union Cities, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 52)
        - DC-AIDS Action Report, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 53)
        - Ballot Initiative Strategy Center, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 54)
        - DC-Alliance for Justice (Box 21, Folder 55)
        - DC-Amnesty International USA (Box 21, Folder 56)
        - DC-NARAL, 1992-2000 (Box 21, Folder 57)
        - GLSTN-Spring Newsletter, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 58)
        - HANDS OFF Washington, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 59)
        - UF Metropolitan Community Churches (UFMCC)/HRCF-UFMCC Partnership, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 60)
        - Independent Political Action (Nat'l Conference on Independent Politics August 1995, Pittsburgh, PA), 1994-96 (Box 21, Folder 61)
        - NGLTF, 1997-98 (Box 21, Folder 62)
        - NOW (National Organization for Women), 1994-97 (Box 21, Folder 63)
        - PFLAG (Box 21, Folder 64)
        - PFAW (People for the American Way), 1996-97 (Box 21, Folder 65)
        - Religious Coalition for Reproductive Choice-"Organizational Assessment", 1997 (Box 21, Folder 66)
        - Right to Privacy, PAC (Portland, OR), 1996-97 (Box 21, Folder 67)
        - Triangle Foundation (Detroit, MI), 1995 (Box 21, Folder 68)
        - Opposition-American Family Assoc. (Box 21, Folder 69)
        - Amer. Public Philosophy Inst. (Box 21, Folder 70)
        - Opposition-Christian Action Network, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 71)
        - Opposition-Christian Voice, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 72)
        - Opposition-Christian Coalition (Box 21, Folder 73)
        - Opposition-Nat'l Coming Out of Homosexuality Day (Kerusso Ministries) (Box 21, Folder 74)
        - Opposition-Coral Ridge Ministries (Box 21, Folder 75)
        - Opposition-Culture Watch (Box 21, Folder 76)
        - Opposition-Family Research Council, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 77)
        - Opposition-Family Research Institute, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 78)
        - Opposition-General Information (Box 21, Folder 79)
        - Opposition-Promise Keepers, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 80)
        - Opposition-Traditional Values Coalition, 1997-98 (Box 21, Folder 81)
    - Field Division, State-by-State Files, pre-1998
      - Alabama (Box 24, Folder 1)
      - Alaska (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - Arizona (Box 24, Folder 3-4)
      - California (Box 24, Folder 5-17)
      - Colorado (Box 24, Folder 18-27)
      - Connecticut (Box 25, Folder 1-4)
      - DC (District of Columbia) (Box 25, Folder 5-9)
      - Delaware (Box 25, Folder 10)
      - Florida (Box 25, Folder 11-14)
      - Georgia (Box 25, Folder 15-16)
      - Hawaii (Box 25, Folder 17-25)
      - Idaho (Box 25, Folder 26)
      - Illinois (Box 25, Folder 27-34)
      - Indiana (Box 25, Folder 35)
      - Iowa (Box 25, Folder 36-38)
      - Kansas (Box 25, Folder 39)
      - Kentucky (Box 25, Folder 40-41)
      - Louisiana (Box 25, Folder 42-45)
      - Maine (Box 26, Folder 1-4)
      - Maryland (Box 26, Folder 5-11)
      - Massachusetts (Box 26, Folder 12-15)
      - Michigan (Box 26, Folder 16-21)
      - Minnesota (Box 26, Folder 22-25)
      - Minnesota (Box 80, Folder 1)
      - Missouri (Box 26, Folder 26)
      - Montana (Box 26, Folder 27-28)
      - Nebraska (Box 26, Folder 29-30)
      - Nevada (Box 26, Folder 31-32)
      - New Hampshire (Box 26, Folder 33)
      - New Jersey (Box 26, Folder 34-37)
      - New Mexico (Box 26, Folder 38-39)
      - New York (Box 26, Folder 40-51)
      - North Carolina (Box 26, Folder 52-55)
      - North Dakota (Box 26, Folder 56-57)
      - Ohio (Box 26, Folder 58-62)
      - Ohio, cont'd (Box 27, Folder 1-6)
      - Oklahoma (Box 27, Folder 7)
      - Oregon (Box 27, Folder 8-21)
      - Pennsylvania (Box 27, Folder 22-25)
      - Puerto Rico (Box 27, Folder 26)
      - Rhode Island (Box 27, Folder 27-28)
      - South Carolina (Box 27, Folder 29)
      - South Dakota (Box 27, Folder 30-33)
      - Texas (Box 27, Folder 34-41)
      - Tennessee (Box 27, Folder 42-43)
      - Utah (Box 27, Folder 44-45)
      - Vermont (Box 27, Folder 46-48)
      - Virginia (Box 27, Folder 49-50)
      - Washington state (Box 27, Folder 51-52)
      - Washington state, cont'd (Box 23, Folder 14-19)
      - Western Regional Targets (Box 27, Folder 53)
      - West Virginia (Box 27, Folder 54)
      - Wisconsin (Box 27, Folder 55-59)
      - Wyoming (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Field Division Events, 1988-2007
      - HRCF Night of 1,000 Gowns (March 1987) Charity Ball for AIDS, 1987-1988 (Box 23, Folder 21)
      - HRCF-Dinner MN, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 22)
      - HRCF-Brunch/Dinner San Antonio, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 23)
      - HRCF-Dinner San Antonio/Austin, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 24)
      - HRCF-Dinner San Antonio, 1992-1993 (Box 23, Folder 25)
      - HRCF-Walk for Life San Antonio, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 26)
      - Dinner-San Antonio/Austin, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 27)
      - HRCF-Dinner New England, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 28)
      - HRCF-Dinner San Antonio, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 29)
      - HRCF-Dinner San Antonio, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 30)
      - HRCF-Dinner Dallas, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 31)
      - HRCF-Dinner Houston, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 32)
      - HRCF-Dinner San Antonio, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 33)
      - HRCF-Dinner San Antonio, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 34)
      - HRCF-misc. (Box 23, Folder 35)
      - HRCF-Dinner New England, 1999-2000 (Box 23, Folder 36)
      - Community Event PR (TX, Wash.), 2001, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 37)
      - Laughing Out Loud (IL), 2002 (Box 23, Folder 38)
      - Fairways to Equality (MD), 2001, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 39)
      - HRC presents basketball games and parties (various states), 2001, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 40)
      - Various community events, CA, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 41)
      - Lina Shore Golf Classic (FL), 2000, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 42)
      - Various HRC Event PR (CA, DC, OK, TX), 2000 (Box 23, Folder 43)
      - Portland, OR film fest, Oct. 1999 (Box 23, Folder 44)
      - Philadelphia Annual Dinner, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 45)
      - Nothing But Net (Philadelphia), 2000 (Box 23, Folder 46)
      - Lina Shore Golf Classic, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 47)
      - South Beach, Miami, FL, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 48)
      - Aspen, CO-Gay and Lesbian Ski Week, 1999-2000 (Box 23, Folder 49)
      - Laguna Beach, CA, July 1999 (Box 23, Folder 50)
      - HRC Gala Dinner and Awards, Los Angeles, CA, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 51)
      - Dallas, TX Black Tie Dinner, 1998-1999 (Box 23, Folder 52)
      - Atlanta, GA Dinner, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 53)
      - Atlanta Dinner, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 54)
      - St. Louis Dinner, 1998-99 (Box 23, Folder 55)
      - Nashville, TN Dinner, FY 1998-99 (Box 23, Folder 56)
      - HRC - Michigan Dinner (Program Book, invitations, tickets), 1998 (Box 23, Folder 57)
      - HRCF Dinner budgets, per event, 1989-90 (Box 61, Folder 2)
      - HRCF Dinner Revenue reports, 1991 (Box 62, Folder 1)
      - 1994 Dinner Co-Chair meeting, 1993 (Box 64, Folder 2)
      - HRCF Connecticut brunch, honoring Kinlock, Stanback, Morales, 1993 (Box 64, Folder 3)
      - HRC Dinner budgets, per event, 1993-94 (Box 65, Folder 1)
      - HRCF Events Program, Policies and Procedures, 1994 (Box 65, Folder 2)
      - Dinner Manager software, 1995 (Box 66, Folder 2)
      - 1996 San Diego Dinner controversy (Box 67, Folder 2)
      - Laguna Beach dinner, 1996 (Box 67, Folder 3)
      - Richmond dinner - HRC/Lambda event, 1996 (Box 67, Folder 4)
      - HRC "Strike Our Helms '96" community bowling event, 1996 (Box 67, Folder 5)
      - HRC - Michigan Dinner, 1995-1996 (Box 67, Folder 6)
      - Cleveland dinner financials, 1995-96 (Box 67, Folder 7)
      - HRC - Tennessee- Nashville Federal Club Brunch, 1997 (Box 68, Folder 1)
      - HRC - Nashville Dinner "2nd Annual", 1997 (Box 68, Folder 2)
      - HRC Event calendar and listings, 1995-98 (Box 69, Folder 1)
      - HRC - North Carolina "Evening in Red" Dinner, 1998 (Box 69, Folder 2)
      - HRC - South Carolina- 1998 Black tie Event (Box 69, Folder 3)
      - HRC - Louisiana HRC- Hawaii Five- O Benefit, 1998 (Box 69, Folder 4)
      - HRC - Louisiana Dinner 1998 (Box 69, Folder 5)
      - HRC - Louisiana Dinner 1998- Boycott (Box 69, Folder 6)
      - HRC Media Coverage & Editorials- Louisiana Dinner, 1998 (Box 69, Folder 7)
      - HRC - Michigan Dinner, 1998 (Box 69, Folder 8)
      - HRC - Austin, TX 1999 Dinner (Box 70, Folder 2)
      - HRC - North Carolina, 1999 (Box 70, Folder 3)
      - HRC - Louisiana Dinner 1999 (Box 70, Folder 4)
      - HRC - Michigan "10th Anniversary Dinner" I, 1999 (Box 70, Folder 5)
      - HRC - Michigan "10th Anniversary Dinner" II, 1999 (Box 70, Folder 6)
      - Dinner Cleveland OH dinner 1999 (Table Captain's Packet), 1998-99 (Box 70, Folder 7)
      - Women's Golf Invitational (Baltimore/Washington), 1999 (Box 70, Folder 8)
      - San Francisco, CA-Dinner, 1998-99 (Box 70, Folder 9)
      - Annual Black Tie Dinner-San Antonio, TX, 1999 (Box 70, Folder 10)
      - Dallas, TX -Black Tie Dinner, 1998-99 (Box 70, Folder 11)
      - National Dinner, 1999 (Box 70, Folder 12)
      - Dinner Binder- New England Dinner (Pt. 1), 2000 (Box 71, Folder 3)
      - Dinner Binder- New England Dinner (pt. 2), 2000 (Box 71, Folder 4)
      - Financial- Portland, Oregon, 1999-2000 (Box 71, Folder 5)
      - Financial- New England Dinner, 1999-2000 (Box 71, Folder 6)
      - Financials- Philadelphia PA Dinner 1999, 1999-2000 (Box 71, Folder 7)
      - Washington Mystics Basketball Game, 2000 (Box 71, Folder 8)
      - Chicago events (Bowling 1999 and Beach Party 2000), 1999, 2000 (Box 71, Folder 9)
      - HRC-Dinner and Fed. Club, 1999, 2000 (Box 71, Folder 10)
      - Dinner Binder- Cleveland OH Dinner, 2000 (Box 71, Folder 11)
      - HRC-General Budget Info, FY 2000 (Box 71, Folder 12)
      - Golf Tournament, St. Louis, MO, 1999-2000 (Box 71, Folder 13)
      - Houston, TX Dinner, 1999-2000 (Box 71, Folder 14)
      - MD-5th Annual Fairways to Equality (part 1), 2000 (Box 71, Folder 15)
      - MD-5th Annual Fairways to Equality (part 2), 2000 (Box 71, Folder 16)
      - Wash, D.C.-Gospel and Soul, 2000 (Box 71, Folder 17)
      - NYC-Feinstein Music Event, 2000 (Box 71, Folder 18)
      - Out Front MN and HRC-Minneapolis WNBA, July 9, 2000 (Box 71, Folder 19)
      - Bowling Party, Chicago, 2000 (Box 71, Folder 20)
      - Comedy Night-HRC Indiana, 2000 (Box 71, Folder 21)
      - HRC Election Watch Party, OK, 2000 (Box 71, Folder 22)
      - Portland, ME, 2000 (Box 71, Folder 23)
      - National Dinner, 2000 (Box 71, Folder 24)
      - Weddings By the Sea-Laguna, 2000 (Box 71, Folder 25)
      - WNBA, 2000 (Box 71, Folder 26)
      - "Ride a Wave to Equality"-Laguna Beach, CA, 2000 (Box 71, Folder 27)
      - Waltz Across TX, 1999-2000 (Box 71, Folder 28)
      - Valentine Boogie-Long Beach, CA, 2001 (Box 72, Folder 2)
      - Final 4-St. Louis, 2001 (Box 72, Folder 3)
      - Laughing Out Loud-Chicago Comedy Night, 2001 (Box 72, Folder 4)
      - Vagina Monologues, 2001 (Box 72, Folder 5)
      - Wash, D.C. "Before Night Falls" Movie Event, 2001 (Box 72, Folder 6)
      - Philadelphia-Dinner, 2001 (Box 72, Folder 7)
      - Annual Dinner 2001-Philadelphia Dinner (part 1) (Box 72, Folder 8)
      - Annual Dinner 2001-Philadelphia Dinner (part 2) (Box 72, Folder 9)
      - When You Wish Upon A Star- 8th Annual HRC Dinner, 1991 (Box 122, Folder 1)
      - The Colors of Freedom II: HRC Dinner, 1994 (Box 122, Folder 2)
      - Come Out for Equality- Dinner and Silent Auction, 1994 (Box 122, Folder 3)
      - Stand Out- 13th Annual Dinner, 1994 (Box 122, Folder 4)
      - Ballroom and Boots- Dinner, 1995 (Box 122, Folder 5)
      - The Colors of Freedom IV: Dinner, 1995 (Box 122, Folder 6)
      - Freedom Cannot Rest- Dinner, 1995 (Box 122, Folder 7)
      - Power Through Unity- Dinner, 1995 (Box 122, Folder 8)
      - Believe in Change- Dinner, 1996 (Box 122, Folder 9)
      - HRC Black Tie Dinner, 1996 (Box 122, Folder 10)
      - Let Freedom Ring! 5th Annual HRC Dinner, 1996 (Box 122, Folder 11)
      - You've Got the Power- 15th Annual New England Dinner, 1996 (Box 122, Folder 12)
      - You've Got the Power: Vote- HRC South Carolina Dinner, 1996 (Box 122, Folder 13)
      - Action= Power, Honesty= Dignity, Love= Family- HRC Dinner, 1997 (Box 122, Folder 14)
      - HRC Black Tie Event- South Carolina, 1997 (Box 122, Folder 15)
      - Illuminate, Educate, Celebrate- Atlanta Dinner, 1997 (Box 122, Folder 16)
      - Silent Auction Catalogue- North Carolina, 1997 (Box 122, Folder 17)
      - Towards a More Perfect Union- HRC Gala, 1997 (Box 122, Folder 18)
      - Visibility Equals Equality- Dinner, 1997 (Box 122, Folder 19)
      - Black Tie Event- South Carolina, 1998 (Box 122, Folder 20)
      - Diversity, Unity, Equality- Dinner, 1998 (Box 122, Folder 21)
      - Embrace Your Place- Dinner, 1998 (Box 122, Folder 22)
      - Evening in Red- Dinner, 1998 (Box 122, Folder 23)
      - HRC Illinois Dinner, 1998 (Box 122, Folder 24)
      - Human Rights Campaign New England Dinner, 1998 (Box 122, Folder 25)
      - Scenes of a Movement- Dinner, 1998 (Box 122, Folder 26)
      - All Equal- HRC Dinner, 1999 (Box 122, Folder 27)
      - A New Millennium- Black Tie Dinner, 1999 (Box 122, Folder 28)
      - Celebrating Our Family Album- Dinner, 1999 (Box 122, Folder 29)
      - Equality in Motion- Dinner and Silent Auction, 1999 (Box 122, Folder 30)
      - It's Time- New England Dinner, 1999 (Box 122, Folder 31)
      - OutReachOut- HRC Cleveland Dinner, 1999 (Box 122, Folder 32)
      - Unity in Equality- Colorado Dinner and Silent Auction, 1999 (Box 122, Folder 33)
      - A New World- Atlanta Dinner and Silent Auction, 2000 (Box 122, Folder 34)
      - Bridges- HRC Illinois Dinner and Silent Auction, 2000 (Box 122, Folder 35)
      - Celebrate the Art of a Movement- Gala Dinner, 2000 (Box 122, Folder 36)
      - Give Birth Again to the Dream- Dinner, 2000 (Box 122, Folder 37)
      - 20/20 Vision- New England Dinner, 2000 (Box 122, Folder 38)
      - An Evening of Purpose and Pride- Dinner and Dance, 2001 (Box 122, Folder 39)
      - The Circus of Life- Black Tie Dinner, 2001 (Box 122, Folder 40)
      - The Future= You- Texas Black Tie Dinner, 2001 (Box 122, Folder 41)
      - HRC Community- Dinner, 2001 (Box 122, Folder 42)
      - HRC Summer Gala, 2001 (Box 122, Folder 43)
      - It's Time- 14th Annual Atlanta Dinner and Silent Auction, 2001 (Box 122, Folder 44)
      - Stand Out, Stand Together- 20th Annual New England Dinner, 2001 (Box 122, Folder 45)
      - 10th Annual HRC Colorado Dinner, 2001 (Box 122, Folder 46)
      - US: One Night, One Event, One Cause- Columbus Dinner, 2001 (Box 122, Folder 47)
      - A Greater Vision- 15th Annual HRC Dinner and Silent Auction, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 48)
      - Celebrate Equality- Cleveland Dinner and Dance, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 49)
      - HRC Auction Guide, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 50)
      - Silent Auction Guide- Boston, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 51)
      - Building Equality, Building Family- 10th Annual Dinner, 2003 (Box 122, Folder 52)
      - Building Our Future: Dinner and Silent Auction Guide, 2003 (Box 122, Folder 53)
      - One Swanky Supper- HRC Illinois Dinner and Silent Auction, 2003 (Box 122, Folder 54)
      - Ring in the Roaring 20's- Dinner and Auction, 2003 (Box 122, Folder 55)
      - White Hot Black Tie- Texas Dinner and Dance, 2003 (Box 122, Folder 56)
      - A Place at the Table- HRC Carolinas Dinner, 2004 (Box 122, Folder 57)
      - Celebrate Equality- 10th Annual HRC Austin Dinner, 2004 (Box 122, Folder 58)
      - Cleveland Dinner and Dance, 2004 (Box 122, Folder 59)
      - Created Equal- Dinner and Silent Auction, 2004 (Box 122, Folder 60)
      - Home= Living, Loving Celebrating- 21st Annual Dinner Gala, 2004 (Box 122, Folder 61)
      - New England Dinner and Silent Auction Catalog, 2004 (Box 122, Folder 62)
      - Turning Point- Illinois Dinner and Auction, 2004 (Box 122, Folder 63)
      - Equality Rising: HRC Phoenix Gala Dinner and Silent Auction, 2005 (Box 122, Folder 64)
      - Freedom is for Everyone- 18th Annual Dinner and Silent Auction, 2005 (Box 122, Folder 65)
      - Imagination- Austin Gala and Silent Auction, 2005 (Box 122, Folder 66)
      - Imagine Tomorrow: Dallas/Fort Worth Black Tie Dinner, 2005 (Box 122, Folder 67)
      - Leading the Way: New England Dinner and Silent Auction, 2005 (Box 122, Folder 68)
      - Less Gab, More Fab- Colorado HRC Dinner and Auction, 2005 (Box 122, Folder 69)
      - Make Them Hear You: 12th Annual Cleveland Dinner and Dance, 2005 (Box 122, Folder 70)
      - Now More Than Ever: 16th HRC Illinois Dinner and Auction, 2005 (Box 122, Folder 71)
      - Tenacious- HRC Carolinas Dinner, 2005 (Box 122, Folder 72)
      - 22nd Annual Columbus Gala Dinner and Silent Auction, 2005 (Box 122, Folder 73)
      - Celebrating the 25th Anniversary of HRC- Austin Dinner and Auction, 2006 (Box 122, Folder 74)
      - Defy Limits- 17th HRC Chicago Dinner and Auction, 2006 (Box 122, Folder 75)
      - Destination- Liberty and Justice for All- Arizona Dinner and Silent Auction, 2006 (Box 122, Folder 76)
      - 15th Annual Colorado HRC Dinner and Auction, 2006 (Box 122, Folder 77)
      - Fire and Ice: 2006 HRC Carolinas Gala Dinner and Auction (Box 122, Folder 78)
      - Truth, Love, Happiness- 19th Annual Atlanta Dinner and Silent Auction, 2006 (Box 122, Folder 79)
      - Voices in Motion- 23rd Annual Columbus Dinner and Silent Auction, 2006 (Box 122, Folder 80)
      - Ain't No Mountain High Enough- San Antonio Dinner and Auction, 1991 (Box 123, Folder 1)
      - HRCF: Auction and Equality Fundraising Dinner, 1992 (Box 123, Folder 2)
      - Stand Out: HRCF TC92- Dinner and Dance, 1992 (Box 123, Folder 3)
      - Family Matters: Washington, D.C. HRCF Dinner, 1993 (Box 123, Folder 4)
      - The Power of Change: The Twin Cities HRCF Dinner, 1993 (Box 123, Folder 5)
      - The Pursuit of Freedom: Houston Black Tie Dinner, 1993 (Box 123, Folder 6)
      - United for Justice: New Orleans Dinner, 1993 (Box 123, Folder 7)
      - We the People: HRCF Saint Louis Benefit Dinner, 1993 (Box 123, Folder 8)
      - Into the Light- HRCF Gala Dinner, 1994 (Box 123, Folder 9)
      - San Francisco HRCF Dinner, 1994 (Box 123, Folder 10)
      - "Voices for Equality... the Stonewall Legacy"- Louisiana Gala, 1994 (Box 123, Folder 11)
      - Full Effort, Full Victory: Twin Cities HRCF Dinner, 1995 (Box 123, Folder 12)
      - Let Freedom Ring: 3rd Annual St. Louis Gala, 1995 (Box 123, Folder 13)
      - San Francisco HRCF Dinner, Dance, and Auction, 1995 (Box 123, Folder 14)
      - A Place at the Table: HRC Nashville Dinner, 1996 (Box 123, Folder 15)
      - One Voice for Equality: HRC 4th Annual St. Louis Dinner, 1996 (Box 123, Folder 16)
      - Out Vote '96- San Antonio Black Tie Dinner, 1996 (Box 123, Folder 17)
      - Ribbons and Rights: HRC Annual Dinner, 1996 (Box 123, Folder 18)
      - Upper Midwest HRC Dinner, 1996 (Box 123, Folder 19)
      - Equality Through Visibility: HRC 1st Annual National Dinner, 1997 (Box 123, Folder 20)
      - HRC Louisiana Black Tie Dinner, 1997 (Box 123, Folder 21)
      - Nashville HRC Dinner- A Place at the Table, 1997 (Box 123, Folder 22)
      - Show Your Stripes: Upper Midwest/ Twin Cities HRC Dinner, 1997 (Box 123, Folder 23)
      - Coming Out Ball- San Francisco, 1998 (Box 123, Folder 24)
      - Equality Through Visibility: LA HRC Dinner, 1998 (Box 123, Folder 25)
      - Focus on Fairness: Tennessee Dinner, 1998 (Box 123, Folder 26)
      - Louisiana Black Tie HRC Dinner, 1998 (Box 123, Folder 27)
      - Moving Toward Equality: Philadelphia HRC Dinner, 1998 (Box 123, Folder 28)
      - 9th Annual HRC Michigan Dinner and Afterglow, 1998 (Box 123, Folder 29)
      - N(ow) Loitering or Electioneering Between This Point and the Poll- NYC Dinner, 1998 (Box 123, Folder 30)
      - Over the Rainbow: 10th Annual San Antonio Black Tie Dinner, 1998 (Box 123, Folder 31)
      - St. Louis- 6th Annual HRC Gala, 1998 (Box 123, Folder 32)
      - Together, Making Equality a Reality- National Dinner, 1998 (Box 123, Folder 33)
      - Upper Midwest HRC Dinner Party, 1998 (Box 123, Folder 34)
      - Celebrating Family Values- Houston Winter Gala, 1999 (Box 123, Folder 35)
      - 11th Annual San Antonio Black Tie Dinner and Auction, 1999 (Box 123, Folder 36)
      - Embracing Our Family, Defining Our Future- Philadelphia Dinner, 1999 (Box 123, Folder 37)
      - Equality=Pride- Northern California Dinner and Auction, 1999 (Box 123, Folder 38)
      - Focus on All Families- Tennessee Dinner and Auction, 1999 (Box 123, Folder 39)
      - Heroes- Black Tie VII- Louisiana HRC Dinner and Auction, 1999 (Box 123, Folder 40)
      - Honoring Our Families- the 3rd Annual HRC National Dinner, 1999 (Box 123, Folder 41)
      - HRC Gala Dinner and Awards Ceremony- Los Angeles, 1999 (Box 123, Folder 42)
      - Ignite Equality- 7th Annual HRC Midwest Gala, 1999 (Box 123, Folder 43)
      - 10th Anniversary Dinner and Silent Auction- Michigan, 1999 (Box 123, Folder 44)
      - Upper Midwest HRC Dinner and Auction- 10th Anniversary, 1999 (Box 123, Folder 45)
      - Celebrating 20 Years- HRC Portland Dinner, 2000 (Box 123, Folder 46)
      - First Annual Seattle HRC Dinner, 2000 (Box 123, Folder 47)
      - Fourth Annual HRC National Dinner- Washington, D.C., 2000 (Box 123, Folder 48)
      - Honoring Women in Politics- Portland Gala Dinner, 2000 (Box 123, Folder 49)
      - Honor, Respect, Community- Tennessee Dinner, 2000 (Box 123, Folder 50)
      - HRC Gala 2000- Los Angeles Dinner and Awards Ceremony (Box 123, Folder 51)
      - I Am Equal- HRC San Francisco Gala, 2000 (Box 123, Folder 52)
      - Once Upon a Time... HRC Louisiana Dinner, 2000 (Box 123, Folder 53)
      - Our Legacy, Our Future- Houston HRC Gala, 2000 (Box 123, Folder 54)
      - Who We Are, Where We've Been, Where We're Going- HRC Dinner- Philadelphia, 2000 (Box 123, Folder 55)
      - Art of Equality- Louisiana HRC Dinner, 2001 (Box 123, Folder 56)
      - Discover Your World- HRC Houston Gala, 2001 (Box 123, Folder 57)